http://www.saversplanet.com/privacy-policy/

HOME FREE SCREENSAVERS TOP SCREENSAVERS WALLPAPERSRussianEnglish3DAnimatedNatureHolidayValentineChristmasNew YearHalloweenAnimalsEffectsSpaceCartoonWaterClockSpringSummerAutumnWinter4k ScreensaversHD ScreensaversHomePrivacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyPersonally Identifiable InformationWe use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.SaversPlanet.com collects no personally identifiable information unless you give it to us when ordering a screensaver or signing up for an email newsletter. No personal information given to us is used for any purpose other than what is stated - to send an email from us related to our club newsletters or to help you with your ordering information. We do not sell, rent, or give your information to any other company for any marketing purposes. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us e-mail at Site VisitorsFor each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes only the consumer's domain name and IP address, but not the e-mail address (where possible). E-mail addresses are then only used by SaversPlanet.com and not sold, rented, given, or shown to any other company for any use whatsoever.CookiesCookies are used on many download links to track referrals from this site. All full version purchases made from these downloads are then credited to SaversPlanet.com from software developer partners on a revenue sharing basis. At this time, SaversPlanet.com does not set any cookies itself.Ad ServersWith respect to Ad Servers: We are currently partnering with Google to deliver ads. We cannot be responsible for the quality of ads or the operation of sites that buy ads through Google.Top ScreensaversButterflies WorldAquatic ClockHappy ClockLive PebbleMore free ScreensaversDownload Windows 10 ScreensaversFree ScreensaversScreensavers Categories. Browse and Download Free Screensavers3D Screensavers14Animated Screensavers45Nature Screensavers35Holiday Screensavers28Valentine Screensavers5Christmas Screensavers14New Year Screensavers12Halloween Screensavers7Animals Screensavers11Effects Screensavers51Space Screensavers7Cartoon Screensavers8Water Screensavers12Clock Screensavers18Spring Screensavers5Summer Screensavers17Autumn Screensavers2Winter Screensavers124k Screensavers28HD Screensavers20 © 2007-2020 SaversPlanet.com. All Rights Reserved.Privacy PolicyEULAHow To UninstallSupportMapLinks
